

ChanHo Park

Full Stack Engineer

Seoul, South Korea +1 (323) 840-1492 · chanho929@outlook.com

⇔ <u>Linkedin</u>				
Date of birt				
Skills React				
JavaScript				
Node.js				
PHP				
Vue.js				
Angular				
Redux				
GraphQL				
MongoDB				
MySQL				
PostgreSQL				
Laravel				
Git				
AWS				

REST API

Express.js

Microsoft Azure

Profile

I am a motivated and innovative web developer with 7 years of experience. Demonstrated talent for front-end and back-end web development to optimize online presence. A seasoned expert in languages such as JavaScript, Typescript, and PHP.

My primary concerns are

- Quality First
- Positive Impact
- Continuous Improvements
- Making ideas come true

Employment History

Senior JavaScript Full-Stack Engineer, Self-employed, Seoul, South Korea

November 2019 - Present

Seoul, South Korea

- Launched 7 React.js, Node.js web applications developed for clients with the best quality.
- Daily maintenance of code, debugging issues, and solving clients' problems
- Consulted web development for business providing custom software solutions and architecture alongside performance optimization
- Accelerated outbound sales cycle by 330% by designing and implementing customer acquisition platform for training and managing technical sales personnel
- Led re-architect effort of a core SaaS product to reduce the platform deployment time for clients by 2 months

Node/React Developer, Cintra Software and Services, Seoul, South Korea

February 2018 — November 2019

- Diversified the company's technology offering from a single product to 4 different ones

CMS		
HTML/CSS		
DevOps		
Typescript		
Languages		
Korean		
English		

- Spearheaded redevelopment of internal tracking system in use by 150 employees, resulting in 20+ new features, reduction of 20% in save/load time, and 15% operation time.
- Managed a team of 10 off-shore and on-site developers across small to medium projects

MERN Stack Developer, Interactive, Seoul, South Korea

April 2015 — January 2018

- Created eye-catching and functional digital design concepts to strengthen company brand and identity.
- Tested websites and performed user testing and troubleshooting prior to live deployment.
- Collaborated with product and marketing teams to redesign mobile onboarding process, improving retention and user experience by 30%.

Full-Stack Web Developer, Urban Ladder, Seoul. South Korea

April 2013 - March 2015

- Develop and test User Interfaces for Mobile/Tablet/Desktop using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQUERY and PHP.
- Build user Authentication and Authorization system using Auth0 API.
- Develop Responsive Websites that could be served by desktop, Tablets and mobile devices using media query.

Education

Bachelor's degree, Seoul National University of Science and Technology, Seoul, South Korea

March 2009 - March 2012